solodev.com 2012-10-02

# Privacy Policy - Boston, Washington DC, Orlando

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") covers how Just Program, LLC d/b/a Solodev (hereinafter, "Solodev") treats personal information that it collects and receives from you during your use of the http://www.solodev.com website ("Site"). Personal information is information about you or your clients that is personally identifiable like name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Such information can include information related to your past use of Solodev products and services. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Solodev does not own or control, or to people that Solodev does not employ or manage. 

#### Collection of Personal Information

When you engage in activities on this Site, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. Your visit to this Site is voluntary and it is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide may be identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity on-line. Accordingly, you will need to use a non-web based option for transacting that business with Solodev.

#### How Your Personal Information is Used

Solodev collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities that you select on the Site. Information that you provide to Solodev may also be used as part of our efforts to keep you informed about product features, software updates or other services offered by Solodev. All information collected will be shared only as required by municipal, state or federal law.

#### Protection of Your Personal Information

Solodev recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Site. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. In addition, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. While information may be saved for a designated period of time, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by municipal, state or federal law.

#### Use of Cookies

You can surf the Site anonymously and access information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we may use "cookies" to assist your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave the cookie to you. A cookie can function as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases and preferences. However, cookies cannot be used to deliver viruses to your computer nor can cookies be executed as code.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies may not be able to access those pages requiring cookies. While certain web pages use cookies to assist your visit to the Site, and while our web servers automatically log the IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally, and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided personal information to Solodev.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Solodev may update this Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent  
notice on our Site.
